<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Indonesian Motorcycle Brands</string>
    // Layout
    <string name="pilih_gambar">(Tap on picture to open gallery)</string>
    <string name="pilih_profil">(Click button to open profile)</string>
    <string name="daftar_brand_judul">Motorcycle Brand List</string>
    <string name="go_back">Back</string>
    <string name="honda">Honda</string>
    <string name="yamaha">Yamaha</string>
    <string name="suzuki">Suzuki</string>
    <string name="honda_list_title">Honda Brand List</string>
    <string name="yamaha_list_title">Yamaha Brand List</string>
    <string name="suzuki_list_title">Suzuki Brand List</string>
    // Data honda
    <string name="verza_brand">CB150 Verza</string>
    <string name="verza_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="verza_deskripsi">Honda GL15B1DF or Honda Verza 150 is a motorcycle produced by AHM Indonesia, this motorcycle is a sport motorcycle equipped with a single cylinder 150 cc SOHC engine and has adopted the PGM-FI fuel supply system.</string>
    <string name="pcx_brand">PCX</string>
    <string name="pcx_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="pcx_deskripsi">Honda PCX is a Honda motorcycle that is intended for the premium scooter segment. When the automatic motorcycle is booming loved by the people of Indonesia in addition to providing convenience for novice riders, various elegant automatic motorcycle designs have also become one of the preferences of consumers in the country.</string>
    <string name="streetfire_brand">CBR150R</string>
    <string name="streetfire_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="streetfire_deskripsi">Honda CB150R StreetFire is a sport motorbike with a 150 cc engine produced by Astra Honda Motor in Indonesia since 2012</string>
    <string name="cbr250rr_brand">CBR250RR</string>
    <string name="cbr250rr_cc">250cc</string>
    <string name="cbr250rr_deskripsi">The Honda CBR250RR is available in a choice of Petrol engines in the new Indonesia Sport from Honda, which comes in 6 variants. Talking about the engine specifications of the Honda CBR250RR, it is powered by two choices of Petrol engines with a capacity of 249.7 cc. CBR250RR is available with Manual transmission depending on the variant</string>
    <string name="crf150_brand">CRF150L</string>
    <string name="crf150_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="crf150_deskripsi">Honda CRF150L is a 150 cc dual-sport series CRF motorcycle made by Astra Honda Motor, a subsidiary of Honda in Indonesia. Launched in November 2017. It shares an air-cooled 149 cc 4-stroke SOHC SOHC 4-cylinder engine with the standard Verza motor.</string>
    <string name="monkey_brand">Monkey</string>
    <string name="monkey_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="monkey_deskripsi">The Honda Z series or Monkey Bike is a line of minibikes made by Honda. Although Honda\'s official model designations are usually the Z50A, Z50J, Z50M, Z50R, and ZB50</string>
    <string name="adv_brand">ADV</string>
    <string name="adv_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="adv_deskripsi">The Honda ADV150 is equipped with an engine with ESP technology, single cylinder, 4-stroke SOHC, liquid cooling with PGM-FI fuel injection technology. With an engine capacity of 149.3 cc, the power that can be produced reaches 14.4 hp at 8,500 rpm and 13.8 Nm of torque at 6,500 rpm.</string>
    <string name="crf250_brand">CRF250 Rally</string>
    <string name="crf250_cc">250cc</string>
    <string name="crf250_deskripsi">Honda CRF250Rally is available in a choice of Petrol engines in Indonesia. The new Off Road from Honda comes in 2 variants. Talking about the specifications of the Honda CRF250Rally engine, it is powered by two choices of Petrol engines with a capacity of 249.6 cc. CRF250Rally is available with Manual transmission depending on the variant. The CRF250Rally is an Off Road 2 seater with a length of 2210 mm, a width of 900 mm, a wheelbase of 1455 mm. as well as a ground clearance of 270 mm</string>
    <string name="cb150x_brand">CB150X</string>
    <string name="cb150x_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="cb150x_deskripsi">Honda CB150X StreetFire is a sport motorbike with a 150 cc engine produced by Astra Honda Motor in Indonesia since 2012</string>
    <string name="ct125_brand">CT125</string>
    <string name="ct125_cc">125cc</string>
    <string name="ct125_deskripsi">Honda CT125 is available in a choice of Petrol engines in Indonesia. The new moped from Honda comes in 2 variants. Talking about the specifications of the Honda CT125 engine, it is powered by two choices of Petrol engines with a capacity of 124.89 cc. CT125 is available with Manual transmission depending on the variant. The CT125 is a 1 seater Moped with a length of 1960 mm, a width of 805 mm, a wheelbase of 1255 mm. as well as a ground clearance of 165 mm</string>
    // Data yamaha
    <string name="monster_brand">YZF R15 MONSTER ENERGY</string>
    <string name="monster_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="monster_deskripsi">This motorbike uses an engine with a capacity of 155 cc, with 6 speeds, and has 4 valves. Another performance on this motorbike is equipped with Variable Valve Actuation (VVA) so that the movement or torque is evenly distributed in every rotation of the engine.</string>
    <string name="yrf_brand">YZF R15</string>
    <string name="yrf_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="yrf_deskripsi">The Yamaha R15 was first introduced in 2014. Indonesia is lucky to be the country where this motorbike is launched globally. Indonesia is also the production base of R15 until now for Southeast Asia</string>
    <string name="wr155_brand">WR 155</string>
    <string name="wr155_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="wr155_deskripsi">Yamaha Indonesia has launched a trail bike in the 155 cc segment, namely the WR155 R. This motorbike is considered to be a strong competitor for the Kawasaki KLX 150 and Honda CRF 150L.</string>
    <string name="xsr155_brand">XSR 155</string>
    <string name="xsr155_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="xsr155_deskripsi">Yamaha took the right step by presenting the XSR 155 in December 2019. The motorcycle received a very positive response from consumers in Indonesia. The launch moment is quite right, at a time when the development of the custom motorcycle world continues to increase</string>
    <string name="mt25_brand">MT25</string>
    <string name="mt25_cc">250cc</string>
    <string name="mt25_deskripsi">Yamaha MT 25 is one of Yamaha\'s newest naked bikes which was first introduced in 2015. Using the Yamaha R15 base, the MT 25 is believed to be Yamaha\'s step to dominate the motor sport market in Indonesia, by providing naked variants on their sport bikes.</string>
    <string name="vixion_brand">VIXION R</string>
    <string name="vixion_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="vixion_deskripsi">Yamaha V-Ixion early presence in the range of 2007 became the first motor sport 150 cc class to adopt a single or mono rear suspension system. This is what makes it impressive sport.</string>
    <string name="vixionmonster_brand">VIXION MONSTER ENERGY</string>
    <string name="vixionmonster_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="vixionmonster_deskripsi">Vixion also gets a Monster Yamaha MotoGP Edition livery, only for the standard version. So the base used is Vixion with a 150 cc engine, not 155 cc with variable valve actuation (VVA) or Vixion R</string>
    <string name="xabre_brand">XABRE</string>
    <string name="xabre_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="xabre_deskripsi">Yamaha Xabre is a sport motorbike with a 150 cc engine from the Yamaha manufacturer. This motorcycle was first introduced in Thailand in December 2015. This motorcycle was then introduced in Indonesia in January 2016, then in the Philippines and Vietnam in August 2016</string>
    <string name="byson_brand">BYSON F1</string>
    <string name="byson_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="byson_deskripsi">Yamaha also has a cheap sport bike called "Yamaha Byson". The price is cheaper than Xabre or Vixion, because it is priced under 25 million Rupiah. Even though it\'s cheap, you will get a powerful and responsive 150cc engine</string>
    <string name="nmax_brand">NMAX 155 CONNECTED</string>
    <string name="nmax_cc">155cc</string>
    <string name="nmax_deskripsi">Yamaha NMAX is an automatic transmission scooter produced by Yamaha in Indonesia since 2015. This scooter was officially launched on February 7, 2015 at Sentul Circuit, Bogor</string>
    //Data suzuki
    <string name="gixer_brand">GIXXER SF 250</string>
    <string name="gixer_cc">250cc</string>
    <string name="gixer_deskripsi">Suzuki Indonesia has marketed a 250 cc sport touring fairing, namely the Suzuki Gixxer SF 250.</string>
    <string name="gxs_brand">GXS-S150</string>
    <string name="gxs_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="gxs_deskripsi">Suzuki GSX S150 is a naked sports motorbike with a 4 stroke engine with a capacity of 150 cc single cylinder DOHC 4 valve engine. Assembled in Tambun, Bekasi Regency, Indonesia by PT Suzuki Indomobil Sales since 2016.</string>
    <string name="satria_brand">ALL NEW SATRIA F150</string>
    <string name="satria_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="satria_deskripsi">The All New Satria F150 now looks more futuristic and sporty with an aerodynamic body design. The more aggressively conquer all the challenges on the road.</string>
    <string name="bandit_brand">GXS150 BANDIT</string>
    <string name="bandit_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="bandit_deskripsi">Suzuki GSX 150 Bandit is a 2 seater Street motorcycle. Available at a price of Rp. 27.3 Million. Suzuki GSX 150 Bandit is available in 1 variant and 4 colors. It is also available in a 6-Speed ​​Manual transmission option.</string>
    <string name="nex_brand">NEX II</string>
    <string name="nex_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="nex_deskripsi">NEX II is the latest stylish automatic motorcycle with a modern and futuristic design. NEX II carries a 115cc FI engine with SEP technology (Suzuki Eco Performance) which provides fuel consumption advantages. NEX II also features the Suzuki Easy Start System which makes it easy to start the engine.</string>
    <string name="addres_brand">ADDRESS F1</string>
    <string name="addres_cc">125cc</string>
    <string name="addres_deskripsi">This new model is an additional option from the existing Suzuki Address FI. This economical and powerful 113cc multifunction scooter is now equipped with 10 color choices of attractive and stylish body panel accessories that can be adapted to the soul and character of today\'s youth.</string>
    <string name="crossover_brand">NEX CROSSOVER</string>
    <string name="crossover_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="crossover_deskripsi">NEX Crossover is the latest automatic motorcycle with a fresh look on the handle bar and seat cover, and still maintains the SEP (Suzuki Eco Performance) technology on the 115cc FI engine. NEX Crossover is also equipped with a Digital Speedometer which makes the appearance more futuristic and makes it easier to read information. </string>
    <string name="playpull_brand">ADDRESS PLAYPUL</string>
    <string name="playpull_cc">125cc</string>
    <string name="playpull_deskripsi">Talking about automatic scooters (scooters) that have many color choices, Suzuki Address is one of them.</string>
    <string name="smash_brand">NEW SMASH F1</string>
    <string name="smash_cc">125cc</string>
    <string name="smash_deskripsi">Suzuki again gave birth to the New Smash FI by maintaining the advantages of performance, toughness and economical fuel consumption with the new tagline \'The pull is powerful!.</string>
    <string name="gxsr_brand">GSX-R150</string>
    <string name="gxsr_cc">150cc</string>
    <string name="gxsr_deskripsi">Suzuki GSX-R 150 is an icon and successor to the tradition of high-performance motor sport that carries technological sophistication. Suzuki applied the principles of the best philosophy when developing the GSX-R from the very beginning, and it is still maintained every time Suzuki develops and creates the next generation model.</string>
    // Data profil
    <string name="nama">Name  :</string>
    <string name="nim">NIM  :</string>
    <string name="prodi">Major  :</string>
    <string name="alamat">Address  :</string>
</resources>